academy.edu 2016-06-29

# Sanford-Brown | Privacy Statement

The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is January 14, 2014.

This and certain other linked web pages on servers owned by Career Education Corporation (otherwise noted as the "Sites") are owned and operated by Career Education Corporation, a Delaware corporation ("Career Education Corporation"). Please read the following sections carefully, as they contain the Privacy Policies covering the use of the Sites. Additionally, you should review our Legal Terms and Conditions. Inquiries or concerns regarding this Privacy policy or the Legal Terms and Conditions may be sent by any of the following: via e-mail to [privacymatters@careered.com](mailto:privacymatters@careered.com) or by mail to Privacy Matters, Career Education Corporation, 231 N. Martingale Road, Schaumburg, IL 60173.

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY (OTHERWISE NOTED AS THIS "AGREEMENT") CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITES. BY USING THE SITES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT ASSENT TO THIS AGREEMENT, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE: [www.sanfordbrown.edu](http://www.sanfordbrown.edu/).

At Career Education Corporation, we share your concerns about privacy. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the site: [www.sanfordbrown.edu](http://www.sanfordbrown.edu/).

### CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.80-1798.84, California residents are entitled to the following rights regarding any personal information collected and used by Career Education Corporation:

Career Education Corporation will notify any California resident of any breach of the security of Career Education Corporation’s system following any discovery or notification of a breach in the security wherein the California resident’s unencrypted information was, or is reasonably believed to have been, acquired by an unauthorized person.

Further, because Career Education Corporation reserves the right to disclose a user’s personal information to any third party in its discretion, all California residents have the right to obtain what information and to whom the information was provided by Career Education in the immediately preceding calendar year. Upon written receipt of a written or email request for such information to the designated address below, Career Education Corporation shall provide a list of any disclosures of the California resident’s personal information to any third party within thirty (30) days of the receipt of such request. The list shall include:

  1. A list of categories of personal information provided to any third party; and
  2. The names and addresses of all of third parties that received the California resident’s personal information within the preceding calendar year.

Such list may be in a standardized format and not specific to any individual.

A California resident’s request for such information may be submitted via e-mail to [privacymatters@careered.com](mailto:privacymatters@careered.com) or by mail to Privacy Matters, Career Education Corporation, 231 N. Martingale Road Schaumburg, IL 60173. California residents shall only be entitled to have this information provided once per calendar year.

### IP ADDRESS

We log all connections to our web servers. Those log files include your IP address. An IP address is NOT personally identifiable information, but general information about your location, connection to the Internet, and your Internet Service Provider. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Sites. Additionally, we will use your IP address to track your navigation of the Sites and we may use your navigation history in current and future marketing efforts to you and to others.

### COOKIES

"Cookies" are small pieces of information stored in a user's browser that give that user a unique identification. The Sites may insert cookies into your browser that identify you as a previous user of the Sites and contain non-personally identifying information regarding you and your navigation of the Sites. In some instances, these cookies may be used by us or other web sites during your future navigation of the internet to target specific advertisements to you based on your previous use of the Sites. The Sites may also read cookies already stored within your browser to identify non-personal information about you and communicate this information to other advertisers. All cookies are established on a per session basis, and are not permanently stored on your machine. For more information about cookies, please visit [www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

U.K. website users can learn more about the sanfordbrown.edu site cookies here.

### CONTACT OR REGISTRATION FORM

Most information contained on the Sites is available without registering or supplying personal information. In the event you affirmatively act to register with one of the Sites or request additional information via the Sites, you agree to the following terms regarding your contact and personal information in addition to the general terms of this privacy policy tied to use of the Sites. The Sites' contact and/or registration forms request that users provide contact and other personal information (such as their name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, education level, educational interests, age, income and marital status). We use this contact and personal information to send the user additional information about our schools and partners. A user's contact and personal information may also be used by us to contact the user directly. We reserve the right to compile and sell the user's contact and personal information to a third party, including the information identified above or other information the user provides to the Sites during the use of the Sites. We will also disclose your contact and personal information when required by law or in response to a request from a law enforcement agency or authority.

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, 15 U.S.C., §§ 6501-06 and 16 C.F.R., §§ 312.1-312.12, our Sites do not permit children under 13 years of age to become users, and we do not collect information from children. By using our Sites, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age.

Except with regard to any contact information you may provide us via the Sites, all comments, feedback, information or materials submitted to Career Education Corporation through or in association with this website (collectively, "Feedback") will be considered non-confidential and the property of Career Education Corporation. By submitting such Feedback to Career Education Corporation, you agree that you assign to Career Education Corporation, without charge, all worldwide rights, title and interest, including copyrights and other intellectual property rights, in and to the Feedback. Career Education Corporation shall be free to use such Feedback on an unrestricted basis.

### TRACKING AND SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share the personal information you provide on the online contact and/or registration forms with a third party vendor to process such information to filter out phony user submissions. The third party vendor stores this information but does not share it with other third parties.

In addition, personal information submitted to Sites related to our universities may be shared with other third-party vendors engaged by us to assist with the development, management, and/or operation of these Sites. These vendors do not share user information with any other company.

Information you provide through the online contact and/or registration forms for a particular school may be shared with other CEC-affiliated schools.

While your browser may also allow you to implement a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) feature through your browser’s settings, our Sites are not configured to honor DNT signals at this time

From time to time, our Sites may link to other websites and we may work with marketing or advertising partners, in which these third parties may collect information about you and/or your computer network over time and across different websites to provide targeted or personalized advertising (also referred to sometimes as online behavioral advertising or interest-based advertising). For a current listing of our partners, please email [privacymatters@careered.com](mailto:privacymatters@careered.com). The practices of these third party companies may be different from ours, and are not governed by this privacy policy. We encourage our users to visit the websites of these companies and/or contact them directly for information about their privacy policies and practices.

### SECURITY

The Sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control; however, Career Education Corporation does not guarantee the performance or adequacy of such security measures.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

The Sites contain links to other web sites that are not owned or operated by Career Education Corporation. Career Education Corporation is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties or the content or security of such web sites. (See the Disclaimers section in our Legal Terms and Conditions).

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy describes the types of information we currently collect, and the ways we use and protect that information. From time to time, we may collect different types of information and use that information in different ways - for example, when we add features or services to [www.sanfordbrown.edu](http://www.sanfordbrown.edu/). In these cases, we may edit this policy to explain the new practices. Because protecting your privacy is very important to us, we do not expect major changes in policy. However, if we do make significant changes in our practices, we will include announcements on the [www.sanfordbrown.edu](http://www.sanfordbrown.edu/) home page so that you will know to review the revised policy.

### CONTACT US

To remove or change your contact information in our database, or to not receive future mailings or other communications, as well as for all other inquiries, please contact us at any time using one of the options below: 

1\. Email webmaster at [webmaster](mailto:privacymatters@careered.com).

### CONTACT US

To remove or change your contact information in our database, or to not receive future mailings or other communications, as well as for all other inquiries, please contact us at any time using one of the options below: 

1\. Email webmaster at [privacymatters@careered.com](mailto:privacymatters@careered.com).

2\. Contact us at:

Career Education Corporation  
231 N. Martingale Road  
Schaumburg, IL 60173  
Phone: 847-781-3600
